《我的生活》前情提要
Previously on This Is Us...
我想成樽你幸福的男人
I wanted to be the man that made you happy.
默F在_始  我要做12分的好丈夫
From here on out, I'm gonna be a 12 for you.
你F在立刻上
You are getting in the car right now,
然后我去@位t生
and we are going to this doctors appointment.
白人
Hi, white people.
我不知道你做@些事是榱耸裁
I don't know what you were looking for with all this,
但我知道你的rg和精力是有限的
but I do know you don't have a whole lot of time.
我想跟孩子f出你的身份
I'd like to tell the girls who you are.
δ碚f  我不是好哥哥  是
I was not a very good brother to you, was I?
你不是
No, you weren't.
但你有rga
But you still got time.
-我叫托比  -我叫P特
- Toby. ?- Kate.
早餐怎么
How's your breakfast?
你是f你做的@粗切燕
You mean this, uh, steel-cut oatmeal and egg-white pancake
有u蛋煎  太好吃了
you're making me eat? It's amazing.
我要去演
I'm gonna do theater.
我I票了
I did it-- I-I-
我了去~s的夜g航班
I booked a redeye to New York.
各位  匹堡市今天很
It's a scorcher out there, folks.
-大家注意避暑  -]嘴
- Stay cool, Pittsburgh. - ?Shut up.
e我]嘴
Don't tell me to shut up.
-你的玩法不  -我]玩e
- You're doing it wrong. - No, I'm not.
-你就是e了  -  好
- Yes, you are. - Mom, I'm hot.
我知道  孩子  爸爸在修空{了
I know, kiddo. Dad is trying to fix the air conditioning.
修得怎么恿  我快崴懒
Babe, how's it going? We're dying in here.
我在努力
I'm working on it.
o我
Give it back!
-你等等  -蛄
- Just hold on. ?- Enough!
m德了我的魔方
Mom, Randall took my Rubik's Cube.
-你玩e了  -好了  我看
- You weren't doing it right. - Enough. Come here.
你Q出淼
You did this?
你吼他才
You're supposed to be yelling at him!
m德  不要狭
Randall, stop scratching.
你起了皮疹  越抓越乐
That's a rash, babe. You're gonna make it worse.
好的  我想到k法了
Okay, I think I have a solution.
修好了  杰克  你怎么...
Is it fixed? Jack, what...
你怎么穿了@件  你明知道我不喜g
What are you doing wearing that shirt? You know I hate that shirt.
我穿@件是因榇┲就很_心
I'm wearing this shirt because it makes me think of fun.
佛_里__浪rg
穿著就想到光
It makes me think of sun.
因槲要去游泳啦
And because we are going to the pool!
P特・皮森  快^
Kate Pearson, you get in here
秀出你的好身材  小美女
and you strut your stuff, young lady.
]e
That's right.
-坌男  -]e就是@  就@
- Care Bears. ?- You know it, you know it.
都好了  今天就是
Today, people, we are gonna debut
坌男鼙然尼的女秀
the brand-new Care Bear bikini!
能不能去G茵泳池
Can we go to the Greenview pool?
跳水板的那  好不好
The one with the diving board? Please.
不行  那地方太了
No, that place sucks.
反正你也基本不下水
You barely get in anyway. ?
三小家伙  你弟弟需要你
The Big Three. Your brother needs you.
e不妨艘黄鹑グ
Come on, you big mope.
eG下我
Don't hold out on us.
求你了  求你了
Please. Please.
好  好  去吧
Okay, okay, yes.
-去Q泳衣  -快去吧
- Go get your swimsuits on. - Go get your suits.
e忘了拿毛巾  毛巾
Come on, towels, towels.
空{完全炝  得找人硇
AC is zonked, babe, we're gonna have to call someone.
去游泳  不看影
Pool, huh? Not a movie?
_定你今天能去游泳池
Are you sure you're okay with the pool today.
我要去泳池度一天假
We're gonna have a day-long pool vacation.
我
I'm gonna snag us
不是一  也不是
not one, not two,
-而是五游泳椅  -五
- but five pool chairs. - Five?
我要去五游泳椅
I'm gonna snag us five pool chairs.
-你可真  -必的
- You bad man. - ?Yes, I am.
孩子自己跑去玩
The kids are gonna run off,
你就可以趁此C看完赡砟阋恢
you're gonna finish that book you've been
-想看完的那本  -《一迷》[好痛苦]- trying to read for two years. ?- It's Misery.
怎么  一定很有意思的
Oh, it's gonna be fun.
不不不
No, no, no,
是f名叫《一迷》  史蒂芬・金的
the book is Misery, by Stephen King.
@影
Oh, yeah, right.
我已把冷鱿溲b好了
Hey, I already packed the cooler.
只э料  不拿啤酒
All soft drinks, no beer.
跟@秃⒆釉谟境卮一天不拿啤酒
A whole day at the pool with those kids and no beer?
我f^  我戒酒了
I told you, I stopped drinking.
我心的可不是你
It's not you I'm worried about.
你看  那就更去了
See? That's what we need, then.
我需要放松一天
We just need a day to relax.
剀疤崾  泳池禁止奔跑打[
A reminder, there is no running,
禁止水  勿yРＡ器皿M入泳池
no diving, and absolutely no glass containers in the pool area.
放松了
Feeling relaxed yet?
有椅子
There's a chair!
快跑  快跑
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
快  太棒了
Go get it! Get it, yes!
到  到  太好了
Get it, get it, get it. ?Yeah!
e叫  才根本不疼
Oh, stop it. That doesn't hurt.
我好像真弄疼你了
Oh, that one might've hurt.
抱歉  乖啦
Sorry. Gotcha.
我想o我梳^l
I want Grandpa to do mine.
]}  安妮小姐
No problem, Miss Annie.
你要硎帐斑@一^剪不嗬磉y
Oh, really? You want Grandpa to try to tame this mess?
-那就戆  -我看看啊
- Have at it. - Let's see here.
@肯定得剪了  z  剪刀在哪里
Oh, that's gotta go. Beth, where's your scissors?
不要
No! ?
那你得坐了  不Sy槲
Then you better sit still and not give me a hard time.
那道疤是怎么回事
How'd you get that scar?
@啊  那天...
Oh, that? Rock, bottle...
石K  瓶子到yw
there were plenty in the air that day.
@故事是不要v了
Maybe we don't tell that story.
]事  @故事挺不e的
Oh, no, it's not a bad one.
一些匹堡市民想改善校接送制度[涉及N族隔x]Some people in Pittsburgh were fighting against bussing,
我也去兔Τ隽α
and I was helping out with that.
那是86是87年
'86, '87?
什么是校接送制度
What's bussing?
就是F人的孩子也能
Getting poor children into the schools
去好W校上W
in better neighborhoods.
你在城市盟工作^
You were working with the Urban League?
是  有段rg
Yeah, a little bit, yeah.
我要去散步了
Look, I gotta get on my walk.
接下砟憷^m
You wanna take over here?
好了  你z  悠戆
Okay, you two, let's get moving.
我和要去上班了
Mom and I gotta get to work
不然可]XI各N美la品了
so we can pay for all this hair product.
-雄著了  -什么情r
- The Eagle has landed. - What's up?
我正式身~s客了  |海岸fq
I'm officially a New Yorker now-- East Coast!
有人要跟你打招呼
Hey, somebody wants to say hi.
P文叔叔  砜次业谋硌莅
Uncle Kevin, come see my play.
我演白雪公主哦
I'm Snow White.
你]_我吧
You're kidding me!
白雪公主是我一直以碜鄣慕巧呢
Snow White's my favorite character of all time!
其我也在橐鲅莩鲈R呢
I'm actually auditioning for a play, too.
鼍胺浅０  也非常接近生活--
Yeah, it's very dark, very, very truthful--
-快W下奶爸的音  -什么
- Do the Manny voice. - What's that?
他喜g你f那句口^U
They love it when you do the catchphrase.
我不想再W奶爸的音了
I don't want to do the Manny voice.
-拜托嘛  -拜托
- Please. ?- Please.
-f什么  -再像一c
- Baby say what? - ?Like, for real.
f什么啊
Baby say what?
不  要像里那
No, like in the show.
在f什么嘛
Baby say what?
超粉z啊
Your biggest fans.
不^不管怎  我已氐赘e@部×
Any... Anyway, this play is a total departure for me,
知道
you know?
奶爸什么的  都一刀嗔
None of that, like, Manny stuff.
@ξ碚f是≈腥宋锏母e
It's a character-driven departure for me.
你在  你看什么呢
Where'd you go? What are you looking at?
兄弟  我得炝
Hey, man, uh, I gotta go.
你就@焖啊
You're just gonna hang up on him?
不不不  我不o你看身份C的
No, no, no, I will not show you my I.D.
除非你告V我  你槭裁匆看
Not until you tell me why you need a reason to see it.
托尼  l生什么事了
Tony, what's going on here?
皮森先生  有人e笏四徘徊
Hey, Mr. Pearson. We had a report of someone loitering.
我]有四徘徊
I wasn't loitering.
我是在散步
I was taking my walk, and literally
_切地f是去品味玫瑰花香
on my way to smell the roses,
-就像上周一  -我知道
- as I have been for the past week. - ?I know.
@里y道有什么禁止p花的法律
Is there some local rose smelling ordinance
-我]f的  -威廉  蛄
- I'm not aware of? - ?William, enough.
蛄
Enough...
他是和你一起的  先生
He's with you, sir?
是的  他和我住一起
Yeah, he's staying with us.
-不好意思  -不好意思
- Sorry. ?- Sorry?
我很抱歉
We're so sorry.
我不知道情r  m德
We didn't know, Randall.
明白  xx
Understood. Thanks.
xx你  托尼
Thank you, Tony.
我得o你I些新衣服了
We're gonna get you some new clothes.
我甘{
I hate kale.
我也是
Me, too.
小芝麻菜和大芝麻菜一与y吃
Baby arugula is just as bad as grown-up arugula.
算了
All right, you know what?
我I伟
Here we go.
不行  不行  我...
Oh, no, no, no. Let me get--
e忘了  你失I了
Remember, you are unemployed.
而且我也不信你能
And I am not convinced that you would do well
-靠乞度日  -你在_玩笑
- begging for money. - Are you kidding?
你不X得司C要是看到
You don't think the drivers will be sympathetic to me
我e著"]吃"的牌子很同情我
holding up a sign that says "Hungry?"
那就好
That's good.
我去下l生g  然后就走  行
I'm gonna use the restroom, and then we'll go, okay?
你^得怎么
How are you?
-挺好的  你呢  -不e
- Uh, good. How are you? - ?Good.
好了  你要走了
Okay, uh... you wanna get out of here?
-那是l  -哪
- Who was that? ?- Who was...
你看到了啊  那是我前妻
You saw that. Uh, that was my ex-wife.
等下  你是f真的
Wait, are you serious?
是啊  我跟你f^我Y^婚
Yeah. I told you I was married before.
可]f是@N
Not to that.
我的生活
第一季  第四集
超模砹  [姿萘  再碡步
Supermodel, pose... and catwalk.
P特  e傻了
Hey, Kate, stop being silly.
快^
Come over here, please.
_曼莎和薇琪也砹
Samantha and Vicki are here!
-坌男  -好了  椅子了
- Care Bears! - Okay, that's two.
H鄣  我是出u肉w才Q淼囊巫
Babe, I had to sleep with someone to get this one.
-希望你原我  -我]}啊
- I hope that's okay. - Yeah, I'm fine with it.
只要他老婆不介意就好
As long as his wife is okay with it.
P文  到你了  把衣服了
Kevin, you're up, please. Shirt off.
槭裁  我都不塾斡
Why? I don't even like swimming.
你不一定^也要下去
You don't have to put your face in.
你可以待在\水^  m德陪你的
You can sit in the shallow end and Randall will stay with you.
我也不喜gm德
I don't like Randall either.
-小P  干嘛呢  -ef了
- Hey, Kev, come on. - Enough.
D^去
Turn around.
m德  到你了
Randall, you're up, please.
^戆
Come here.
D身
Turn around, please.
你_定我需要涂防袼
Are you sure I really need sunscreen?
-肯定要  -要啊  然
- Yes, absolutely. ?- Yeah, absolutely.
你然要涂了
Of course you do. Sure.
三小家伙  快^
Okay, look, Big Three, come here.
^  你周有很多大人
Come here. You are surrounded by adults
和同邮谴笕说木壬T
and lifeguards that resemble adults.
你不遇上...
There's very little trouble you can actually get into--
等等  等下  P特
Wait, wait. Kate, baby,
你_定不再套件衣服
are you sure you don't want to put a shirt on?
-好吧  -o
- Right. - ?Here.
好好看你的吧
Enjoy your Misery.
大家都盯著她的泳衣看  杰克
People are staring at her in that bathing suit, Jack.
那些小混球一定f三道四的
Some jerky little kid is gonna say something.
那只是悍
It's baby fat.
她才八q  孩子@菏裁炊疾欢
She's only eight years old. Kids haven't turned mean yet.
P文最近是怎么了  B度那么差
And what is up with Kevin lately, and that attitude?
-他太嫉妒m德了  -他]事
- He's so jealous of Randall. - He's fine.
他]事  他仨都很好
Babe, he's fine. They are all fine.
有m德需要抹防袼
And does Randall need sunscreen?
@些年砦都是在他身上浪M防袼
I mean, have we just been wasting sunscreen all of these years?
@我也不知道
That I have no answer for.
椅子  椅子
Chair. Chair!
小心c
Careful!
她只是他的前妻  P特
She's his ex-wife, Kate.
好  PI字是"前"
All right? The operative word being "Ex."
他已x婚了  他F在和你在一起
They're not together anymore. He's with you now.
可槭裁茨  你真瞧瞧她
"Why?" is the question. You should see her.
P文
也S那才是托比想要的
Maybe that's what Toby wants.
也S他看上我是榱M足他的胖妞癖
Maybe he's fulfilling a fat-girl fetish with me.
_有@N癖好
Well, that's actually a thing.
然  ξ碚f
Of course, for me it was
那更像是一A段  但也差不多
more of a phase than a thing, but anyway...
我仔{查了下@女人
I did a deep dive with this woman.
她的一切都如此完美
Everything reeks fabulous.
完美的品位  完美的朋友
She has fabulous taste, she has fabulous friends.
她去^阿根廷  P文
She's been to Argentina, Kevin!
我f  我把你留在洛杉
Listen to me, I did not leave you in Los Angeles
不是你自我糟`的
so you could self-sabotage, okay?
所以so把WP掉  立刻R上
So get off the Internet-- do that right now--
告V我怎么做才能通^R
and tell me how hard I'm gonna crush this audition.
消失了
The edges are gone...
事情也S之l生了
and then the thing.
xx你  肖恩・帕特里克
Thank you, Sean Patrick.
我X得有人挺不e
Some good choices, I thought.
丹尼不e  其他人演得透了
It's Daniel. Everyone else sucks.
其我更喜g...
You know, I kind of liked--
就x丹尼
It's Daniel.
稍等  稍等
Hold on, hold on.
有一位  P文・皮森
We have one more. Kevin Pearson.
Σ黄  我知道  很抱歉我t到了
Sorry. I know, I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm late.
我本硐胱地F  再一路走^
It's just, you know, I tried to take the subway, right,
像~s客那
and then walk, like a New Yorker.
我是_恩・希勒
Ron Shiller.
@位是斯隆・桑德伯格
This is Sloane Sandberg.
-你就是  -∽骷
- You're the, uh, screenwriter. - Playwright.
你是要~出第一步的
Well, you know, I mean, you gotta start somewhere.
今天你和梅英小姐  如果你不介意的
You'll be reading with Miss Maine today, if that's okay.
然  和l都行
Yeah, no, whatever you got, you know.
因州小姐  酆扇A州小姐
Miss Maine, Miss Iowa.
我曾ux^支持特朗普美小姐
I judged, uh, Miss USA for Trump once,
所以我可能^面
so we may have actually met before.
梅英小姐全名是W利S・梅英
Miss Maine is Olivia Maine.
托尼提名@得者
Tony nominee.
她扮演杰西卡
She plays Jessica.
然  你好  很高dJR你
Of course. Hi. Good to meet you.
在_始之前  我有...
Well, before we start, I just wanted to...
我有拙湓必要f
I want to get something off my chest.
我知道你的看法
I do understand the perception, you know.
洛杉的演T淼竭@里
These L.A. actors, they come out here, right?
≡豪镫S便演小角色
They do their little quick stint in theater
只M足自己的s心
just to feel better about themselves.
而我s不是  好
That's not why I'm here, okay?
我磉@是有正理由的
I'm here for the right reasons.
那我so把@ν臧  可以
Let's get this over with, shall we?
你想我先_始
Did you want me to start?
]e  我X得那颖容^好
Yes, I thought it would be good, if,
你先f  我后f
you speak, then I speak,
接著你再f  然后我就可以回家了
then you speak, and we all go home.
你X得可以
Does that work for you?
行啊  很好
Yeah. That's great...
我的有c模糊了  @一天在太漫L了
My recollection's hazy, actually, it was a long day.
我可不是  早上九c前我的一天就Y束了
Not for me. Mine was over before 9:00 in the morning.
你的口音真棒
That's really good... accent.
-你f什么  -美口音
- What? - ?The American accent.
什么
What?
我正...  努力融入角色
I just... diving... diving right back in.
_~是...  "我躺在"  我不...
It say, uh... it says "I lay," uh, I don't...
我f...我不需要f@  _~是...
Let me just say... I don't need to say it. It says...
我是f吧
I'll just say it.
我躺在...
I lay...
^m^m
Just keep going.
真是...
This is...
我能搞定
I'll get it.
我整夜躺在a^上
I lay on the dock all night,
直至天明
and part of the next morning.
s感受不到任何|西
And I don't feel a thing.
我再硪槐
Let me take that again.
我的天  我的天
Oh, my gosh... Oh, my gosh.
好的  f什么...
Okay. Baby say what...
好了  我躺在...  我j下
Okay. I-I lay... Let me get into it.
我整夜躺在a^上直至天明
I lay on the dock all night and part of the next morning.
s感受不到任何|西
And I don't feel a thing.
蚊x叮咬  皮w  都]有感X
The bug bites, the sunburn. Nothin'.
就像我以前一起去~r  你得
It's like when we used to go fishing. You remember?
-我]^~  -你是下一句...
- I never fished... - Do you have the next...
-你搞什么鬼  -Σ黄
- What the hell? - ?Sorry.
你]f  我以...
You weren't talking, so I thought...
@叫停D
It's called a pause.
是
Right.
抱歉  我的”旧]有停D...
Sorry. It doesn't say pause on my script...
上面也]呢  可我F在不就是@
Well, it doesn't say suck, either, yet here we are.
你知道你的尺a
You know your size?
我是挑修身的穿
Always tended toward the slim.
估F在也]吧
I don't see that changing much at this point.
@些
Try these.
完了我路去一趟店
Afterwards, we'll swing by the pharmacy,
把t生o你_的拿了
get those medications that the doctor wrote for you.
起硗好的
Sounds like a plan.
一百美元
$100?
就是@r
It's what they cost.
我I  你就I吧
I'm paying, just take the pants.
我要不要
So are we gonna talk about it or not?
什么
Talk about what?
什么  今天早上的事
About what. Uh, this morning.
是你就想臭著s什么也不f
Or are you content to stand in silent judgment with that face?
我的平r就@
It's just my face.
不  你是不喜g我替你道歉
No, you didn't like me apologizing for you.
我懂
I get it.
如果我把事情[大你是不是就高d了
Would you have been happier if I made a big scene?
揍托尼一D
You know, got up in Tony's face,
把警察招砣缓χ我水
had the cops roll up and turn the hoses on us?
他是卡斯格拉夫一家
It's the Cosgroves.
先生_了一家保U公司  妻子收藏^
He runs an insurance agency, she collects owls.
v史可不站在我@一
History would not have memorialized our stand.
你被水^
You ever had a hose turned on you?
很抱歉  我]有^
Can't say that I have, I'm very sorry.
不要L  很疼的
Don't be. It hurts.
就是@表情
And there's that face.
我就是@N表情  我想I纂pm子
Only face I got. Look, I could use some socks...
@表情  就好像是在f你胳膊上
No, the face. The one that says I have a scar
有年樗秃⒆上W留下的疤痕
on my arm from integrating schools.
f不定_上有樽杂捎涡r留下的水泡
And probably blisters on your feet from marching for freedom,
至于我  因槲页砷L于白人家庭
but me, because I grew up in a white house,
你就J槲也欢黑人的生活
you think I don't live in a black man's world.
你知道你是什么表情
Oh, you know the one.
你的表情那IIT奈MT那一刻起
The one where that salesman there has been eyeballing us
就一直盯著我
ever since we came in here.
有那保安的位置挪恿艘稽cc
Or where that security guard has moved just a little
只楦好地O我
off his mark so he can keep us in his sight.
有他肯定在我付X的r候
And where they'll definitely ask
我出示信用卡的用糇C明
for an ID with my credit card when I go to pay,
M管他]向其他人提出^@拥囊求
even though they haven't asked for anybody else's.
再加上每天似@拥o导小事
Plus a million things every day
我都要xo
that I have to choose to let go,
@游也挪把自己馑
just so I'm not pissed off all the time.
就像我今早在街上做的一
Like I did on the street this morning.
就和我每天做的事一
Like I have done every day of my life.
快去你的修身o褶休e吧
Now try on the damn slim cut flat front chinos.
你穿著肯定好看
I think they'll look nice on you.
m德
Randall
看
Watch!
太酷了
Cool! Cool!
爸  看我  爸
Dad, watch! Dad!
-另外一去哪毫  -我在找
- Where's the other one? - I'm looking.
天啊  只要一秒不盯著一
Man, you take your eyes off one for a second,
其他的就也都不了
you lose track of the others.
那是因樗人
That's because there are more of them
比咱z多呀
than there are of us.
永h都是@
Always will be.
什么
What? Oh.
在f孩子呀
Talking about the kids.
是啊  他人多荼
Yep. It's a war. They got the numbers.
-爸爸  爸爸  -我]_始就累趴了
- Dad! Dad! - We were beat before we started.
-看我  -她在那耗
- Watch! - There she is.
你好
Hi. Hey, guys.
想玩美人~
You want to play mermaids?
@是我所有人o你的
This is from all of us.
爸爸
Dad!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Daddy! Dad!
爸爸  快看我
Dad, watch me!
好  我看你了
Yeah. I see you, pal!
得他第一次叫我爸爸的r候
Do you remember the first time he said "Dad"?
我有多高d
How happy I was?
m德去哪毫
Now where's Randall?
怎么  你看了
How about that time? Did you see?
小P  你弟弟呢
Hey, Kev. Where's your brother?
我不知道
I don't know!
杰克
Jack.
你去岸上找  我看看水里
You take land, I'll take sea.
爸爸  快看我
Dad! Watch!
P文
Kevin.
你互相照看Ψ降
You were supposed to watch each other!
m德
Randall!
P特  @真是史上
Kate, it was the worst audition
最糟糕的一次面了
in the history of the world. Okay?
那女的搞得我超o
I mean, that woman made me so nervous,
中途我居然oo故地
I started doing an English accent
f起了英式口音
in the middle of it for no reason!
肯定]有那么糟吧
Okay, I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
也S@才是}所在
Maybe that's the problem. You know?
-我太想得到@角色了  -@不是奶爸
- I wanted it too much. - Hey! It's the Man-ny!
奶爸  最近怎么
Hey Man-ny! How's it going?
著  你能不能坐wC^
Yeah. Listen. Could you please fly out here?
我F在真的很需要你
I really need you right now.
你]事的  只要...
You'll be fine, you just...
我只要什么  怎么不f了
What? I'm just what? Where'd you go?
出售
]什么  我在逛街
Nowhere. I'm here. I'm shopping.
-我好迷茫  -你@不是迷茫
- I'm lost. - You're not lost.
只是一切δ碚f都太陌生了
It's just all new. It's just new.
不是  我是f我真的迷路了
No... I mean I'm actually lost,
我完全不知道我F在在哪  我先炝
I have no idea where the hell I'm at. I got to go.
抱歉
Sorry. Oh.
l生的事  我想f
That whole thing back there, just so you know.
我其]那么  好
I'm not actually bad, okay?
-好  我知道了  -好的
- Okay. Duly noted. - Okay.
我只是想跟你f明白
Okay. Just wanted to get that out there.
好了  你f完了
Well, out there it is.
不^你也]有蜕鲜裁疵
Although you weren't super helpful.
你想喝一杯
You want to get a drink?
F在
What, like, now?
]e  就F在  走吧
Yeah. Now. Come on,
-洛杉男孩  -好
- L.A. - Yeah.
xd
伍德德∩g迎您
演出快_始了
Mom, the play's about to start!
好吧  苔z  快c
All right, Tess. Hurry up.
快去把裙子Q上  拿好她的鞋
Go get your dress on. Get her shoes.
-快快快  -祝你演出成功
- Hurry, hurry, hurry. - Break a leg.
加油
Come on...
@地方真不e
This is a nice place.
是啊  @片地^的公立W校很不e
Yeah. Public schools in this area are good,
所以我才搬磉@里
It's why we moved here.
甚至比私立的更好
Even better than private.
父母能完全⑴c到孩子的成L中
You know, the parents are real involved.
z是董事的一T
You know, Beth's on the board.
完全⑴c其中
Real involved.
W校有r
They got a farm.
-真的  -  就在教W呛竺
- Really? - Yeah, out back.
孩子能蛄私馔恋  H手N植食物
Kids learn about the land. Grow their own food.
xx
Thank you.
r隼镞B了u
They got, uh, chickens.
有一^山羊
They got a goat.
需要椭
Can I help you find something?
不用
No.
你是想工作的事吧
You're here about the job.
我@里的招工啊
You know. The job?
]e
Y-Yeah.
太好了
Great!
那我去那聊一聊
Let's go over here so we can talk.
m德
Randall!
P特  你看m德了
Kate, have you seen Randall?
m德
Randall!
我不想和你一起玩
因槟我很G
_曼莎
m德
Randall?
Randall...
m德
Randall! Hello!
你]到我叫你
Did you not hear me calling you?
-你在@焊墒裁茨  -不不不
- Hey, what are you doing over here? - Oh, no, no, no...
-我到...  -]事的  我看著他呢
- I've been... - It's okay. I'm watching him.
好的  F在有我碚疹他了  抱歉
Okay, it's... I-I have him now. I'm sorry,
我是他  我差c牧  我叫卡
I'm his mother. I was a little panicked. I'm Rebecca.
我知道你是l
We know who you are.
你知道
You do?
]e  如果一白人家庭е一黑人小孩
Oh yes. When a white family has a black child
也]有向我介B^自己
and they don't introduce themselves to any of us,
我一般都多加注意
we tend to take notice.
xx你照看他
Well. Thank you for watching him.
只是他不在@旱
He's just not supposed to be over here.
不是f@里有什么不好
Not "over here" like that.
磉@]什么不
There's nothing wrong with over here.
我的意思是他待在我的范
I just mean that I want him where we can see him,
也就是我坐的地方  我面前
where we're sitting, in front of us.
xx你  很高dJR你
Thank you. It was very nice to meet you.
m德  戆  我走
Randall, come on. Let's go.
戆  xx你
Come on. Thank you.
等等  你在@等一下
Actually, you stay right here.
那是我的鹤  我是他
That's my son, and I'm his mother.
我不知道你是不是
And I don't know if you have
@拥募彝ビ惺裁匆庖
some sort of problem with that arrangement,
但是我真的不在乎
but also, I don't really care.
之xx你臀艺湛次的孩子
Thank you very much for watching my son.
但F在由我碚疹他了
But I have him now.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
你Ш⒆蛹粢合m的l型了
You need to get the child a proper haircut.
剃刀都把他脖子了
The razor bumps on his neck.
你需要找知道怎么理黑人^l的理l店
You need a barber who knows how to cut black hair.
走吧
Come on.
我跟你f了你跟哥哥待在一起  不是
I told you to stay with your brother, didn't I?
Σ黄
Sorry.
@就是你想磉@泳池  不去其它泳池的
Is this the real reason you wanted to come to this pool
真正原因
and not the other?
走吧
Come on.
白雪公主
真美啊
So beautiful.
您好呀  敢姑娘芳名
Ho, there. Who might you be, fair maid?
我是白雪公主
I am the Princess Snow White.
我周游四方
I have traveled this land and many others,
奈匆^如此一位肌w如雪的美人
and never have I seen a beauty so fair.
@位士  您又是哪睦砟
Where are you from, noble sir?
您淼竭@森林中又是所楹问履
What errand brings you to the forest?
我碜赃bh之地
I come from a land far away.
-那...  -xx
- The, uh... - Thank you.
那部≌娴暮芴e
That play is really special, isn't it?
我的意思是  m然我]有x^很多”
I mean, I don't read a lot of plays,
-但那很不e  -我明白
- but that's -- that's good. - Yeah. Yeah, I got that.
著  那部...
No, look, it's...
真的很棒
it's really good, actually.
我是f  很精致
I mean, it's... it's fragile.
微妙而致
It's -- it's delicate.
你哪睦淼  P文・皮森
So, where are you from, Kevin Pearson?
我
Me?
我老家在匹堡
Uh... Pittsburgh, originally.
你的家人在匹堡
You got family back there?
F在不在了
Um... not anymore.
所以F在你以洛杉榧伊
Right, so, L.A. is home now?
是吧
Yeah, I guess so.
是啊
Yeah.
我X得你回去
I think you should go back there.
我知道
I know, right?
你是J真的
Are you serious?
我是J真的
I am serious.
而且是以朋友的身份告V你
And I'm telling you this as a friend
因檫@N事我得太多了
because I see this all the time.
你自己也f了
I mean, you said it yourself.
演^『碗影的哥美女淼竭@
Pretty people come here from TV or movies
因樗想睃c真格的
because they want to do something real.
即便他...
I mean, even if they've...
他一子都不曾真\^
they've never had a genuine moment in their entire lives.
你知道他明白了什么
Do you know what they find out?
猜猜看
That guess what?
太y了
It's hard.
在是太Dy了
It's so hard.
并不是...
It's not...
不是b出淼
it's not pretend,
1955年美著名喜∑
@可不是在高中食堂里演什么《t男G女》
it's not Guys and Dolls in some high school cafeteria.
不是...
It's not...
不好意思  你演的那部影叫什么碇
I'm sorry, what-what-what was the-the movie you were in?
H上是部
It was a TV show, actually,
名叫《n男保姆》
called, uh, The Man-ny.
是啊  我f
Yeah, and look,
我不是f
I'm not saying that
@角色你演得不好
you're not good at what you do.
我相信你肯定...
I'm sure you're...
肯定非常出色
you're great at it.
我就演不了@角色
I mean, I-I couldn't do it.
但你演『瓦@里是纱a事
But this... is not that.
你的能力不
You're in over your head,
P文・皮森
Kevin Pearson.
如果你真想演@  就回家去
I mean, if you really want to do this, then go home,
班  W一下
find a class, get some training.
我是f
I'm just being honest.
我懂了
I see.
以朋友的身份
As a... as a friend.
-是的  -好吧
- Yeah. - Yeah.
可我是X得
Still, just, you know, it feels like
"朋友"@~你用e了
you're using the word "Friend" wrong.
出什么事了
Everything all right?
-你好  -好
- You okay? - Yeah.
真的
Yeah?
好著呢
Yeah.
你拿到了那角色
You got the part.
等一下  不好意思  你f什么
Wait, I'm sorry, what?
他X得"保姆"硌豳u
They think the nanny will sell tickets.
其是《n男保姆》
It was actually The Man-ny.
爸  快看  我要下去了
Dad, look! I'm going under and everything!
爸爸
Dad!
-我看著你呢  伙  -m德
- Yeah, I see you, pal! - Randall.
-爸爸  -午
- Dad! - Lunch, baby.
-爸爸  -也S她只是
- Dad! - You know, maybe she was just
-想忙  -爸爸  看我
- trying to be helpful. - Dad! Watch!
居高R下地教我怎么B孩子  就@么兔
By condescendingly telling me how I could raise my kid? Yeah.
-不了  xx  -爸爸
- No, thank you. - Dad!
*我畚野职  很酆鬯*
*I love my father and I love him well...*
*希望不久后的某一天能到他*
*I hope to see him someday soon*
*我畚野职  很酆鬯*
*I love my father and I love him well*
*希望不久后的某一天能到他*
*I hope to see him someday soon*
*因槲易〉牡胤  到了晚上又黑又暗*
*'Cause where I live  It gets dark at night*
*那N黑暗吞噬光明*
*The kind of dark eats up the light*
*我住的地方  到了晚上又黑又暗*
*Yeah, where I live  It gets dark at night*
*那N黑暗吞噬光明*
*The kind of dark eats up the light*
*你知道的*
*And you know that, mother*
*我在fe*
*I'd be lying*
*如果我f我不怕夜晚*
*If I didn't tell you I'm afraid of night.*
P特  你怎么不吃|西
Kate, you're not eating.
你好
You okay?
她怎么了
What's up with her?
逗我呢吧  槭裁
Are you kidding me?! Oh! Why?
因槲]她穿T恤  就因檫@
Because we didn't make her wear a T-shirt, that's why.
不  杰克  @只情r更糟
No, no, Jack, you're only gonna make it worse.
坐下
Sit...
坐下  真的
Sit down. Seriously.
我差c就淹死了
I almost drowned!
-什么  -你留意^我
- What? - Did you even care?
-什么r候  -我都要到池底去了
- When? - I tried to get to the deep end,
-可你看都不看我一眼  -冷o下
- but you never watch me. - Hey. Calm down.
-你是盯著他  -P文  P文
- You always watch them. - Kev, Kev, Kev.
-好了  -e碰我
- Come on... - Don't touch me.
心c  孩子
Watch yourself, pal.
你一直忙著不P特吃得太多
And you're so busy making sure that Kate's not eating too much...
P文  冷o一下
Kev, calm down.
要不m德X得自己是被IB的
and... and Randall's not too adopted,
可@r候P文去哪了呢
and meanwhile, where's Kevin?
你猜猜看
Oh, guess what?
他死了
He's dead.
孩子  我勰  我看著你呢
Bud, we love you. We were watching...
e碰我
Don't touch me.
交o我吧
I got this one.
^  ^
Hey, come here. Come here.
-干什么  -抱歉  抱歉
- What? - I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
好  我一直看著你的
Okay? I should have been watching.
-好  -你是看著我
- Okay? - You should have.
我承Je`  我一直看著你
And I said I was and I should have been watching you, pal.
我在努力  好
I'm trying, okay?
我f  我知道我比你年o大
Look, I know that I'm bigger than you.
我知道我是成年人了
I know that I'm an adult,
但我也是第一次v@些  好
but I... th-th-this is my first time, okay?
我也是第一次
This is my first time, too.
我有了你三  我在努力
I got three of you and I'm trying.
Σ黄  我本在你身的
I'm sorry. I should've been there.
我以后都在你身的  好
And I'm gonna be there, okay?
好
Okay.
能o我一肀
Can I have a hug?
能f句"爸爸我勰"
Can I get a "Dad, I love you"?
你有理l的名字
Do you have the name of a barber?
有
I do.
┠愀嬖V我
Well, I would appreciate it.
我o你
Then I'll write it down.
他上岸之后
When he gets out of the pool,
你得o他涂c乳液
you need to put lotion on him
不然皮w灰
or he gets ashy.
乳液  好的
Lotion. Okay.
xx
Thank you.
我鹤悠r放W后
Do you think that my son could play with yours
能跟你家小孩一起玩
sometime after school?
然
Yeah, yeah.
]}
I think we can do that.
有他到底需不需要涂防
And does he need sunscreen or not?
是要的吧
He does, right?
我X得要
I thought he did.
我就知道
I knew he did!
你能臀腋我老公ff
Can you tell my husband that, please?
我]Шv  抱歉
Uh, I didn't bring a resume, sorry.
我不知道要面
I didn't think I'd have a job interview.
我以榫褪悄申表
And I thought I would just pick up an application...
既然都砹  那就聊聊吧
Oh, well, you're here and I'm here, let's talk.
你皮w真好
You have really pretty skin.
xx
Oh, thank you.
你也是
So do you.
xx
Thanks.
P特  你ξ液臀业牡甑谋尘坝辛私
So, Kate, do you know anything about my store or my background?
一cc
Hmm... A little.
我知道你在2013年_了@家店
I know that you've had this store since 2013
在@之前你_W店u你的立O
and before that you sold your own designs on Etsy,
直到后砟愀人合伙
until you partnered with that woman
是你加州大W圣克分校的同W
that you met at UC Santa Cruz--
加油  香蕉蛞蝓[UCSC吉祥物]go, banana slugs--
你去泰⒓恿怂的婚Y
at her wedding in Thailand.
太美了
Oh, so beautiful.
直是粝胫旅
Like, that is my dream trip.
后砟氵M口了@些巾
And then you imported those scarves
生意拇俗呱狭苏
then it just, like, took off from there.
有你x婚了  ]有小孩
Oh, and you're divorced, you have no kids
你戴檐帽的幼犹好看了
and you look amazing in wide-brimmed hats.
我猜的
I assume.
你^型很m合
You just have the head for it.
我不m合  我戴著就像奶嘴
I don't. I look like a pacifier.
我喜g面前做足功n的人
I like a person who does her research before an interview.
我最做功n了
I'm a big researcher.
好
Hey, what's up?
好消息是我找了份工作
So, the good news is: I got a job.
意思是有南息
Well, that means that there's bad news.
澜奔跑
成人游泳rg
Adult swim.
小孩都上岸
Adult swim only.
你冷
You cold?
T恤呢
T-shirt?
我]
I didn't bring one.
那...
Well...
我Я思T恤
I brought a T-shirt.
@件
That's the one Mommy hates.
只是妒忌
Oh, Mommy's just jealous.
我不X得
I don't think so.
是真的
Well, it's true.
她只是假b
She just pretends like she hates it
因槲也唤o她穿
because I won't let her wear it.
你知道@件衣服哪淼
You know where I got this shirt?
我f是a君子流浪h的
I heard Mommy say it was from a drugged-out drifter.
不太了解情r
Listen, Mommy doesn't know the whole truth,
你e跟e人f  好
so this is gonna have to stay between us, okay?
我r
I got it...
在佛_里_
in Florida.
一叫代托{比奇的神奇的地方
A magical land called Daytona Beach.
我能去那
Can we go there?
不行
No.
你不能去代托{比奇
No, you may never go to Daytona Beach.
我要你大f出
I want you to say it out loud:
"爸爸  我^Σ蝗ゴ托{比奇"
"Daddy, I will never go to Daytona Beach."
爸爸  我^Σ蝗ゴ托{比奇
Daddy, I will never go to Daytona Beach.
乖
Good girl.
我r就在那
But I was there...
一天晚上  我在回酒店的路上
and one night, I was walking back to my hotel,
然后遇了一人
and... I came across this man...
一旅客
a traveler.
他穿得破破的
He was wearing ragged clothes
口音很奇怪
and he had a strange way of talking.
有三牡霸谄圬他
And these three young jerks were bothering him.
他想拿走他的一袋生活用品
They were trying to take away his bag of groceries.
所以我把那些牡摆s跑了
And so... I chased the jerks off.
你一人
By yourself?
是的  就我一人
Yeah, by myself.
我之前喝了妆
And I had a few...
S他命料  把他s跑了
vitamin drinks and... I chased them off.
真事
It happened.
@旅客非常感激
And the traveler was so grateful,
想蟠鹞
he wanted to repay me.
但他有的|西不多
You know, he-he didn't have much,
所以他把手伸M他的小包里
so he reaches into his little satchel
掏出了@件衣服
and he pulls out this shirt.
他跟我f@是件有魔法的T恤
He says to me that it's a magic T-shirt.
他f
He said,
你穿上它的r候
that when you wear it,
你的κ志看到你希望他
your enemies will see you exactly as
看到的幼
you want to be seen,
而且只能看到那幼
and only that way.
o你想成槲涫恳埠
Whether it's a... a warrior,
公主也好
or a princess.
任何形象都行
Whatever you want.
-真的有用  -你f呢
- Does it work? - You tell me.
我遇你那晚  就穿著@件衣服
I was wearing this shirt the night I met your mom.
她rX得我是世界上最的男人
And she thought I was the handsomest man in the world.
-你  -是啊
- You? - Yeah, I know.
就是我
Me.
魔法
Magic.
我x褡龉主
I'm gonna go with princess.
你得知道...
I want you to know...
就算]有@件衣服
that your daddy already sees you that way
你也一直是爸爸的公主  你不需要它
without the shirt, okay? You don't need it.
xx爸爸  不^我是要穿著它
Thanks, Daddy, but I'm gonna wear it anyway.
好啦
Okay.
公主陛下
Your Highness.
我斫o你找皇冠
Need to find you a crown.
老天  @不可能
Oh, my God, this is not happening.
@事...  你真的...
This is-- are you-- oh.
托比
Toby.
你是在告V我
So you're telling me
你要槲仪捌薮蚬
that you work for my ex-wife?
我原]@打算  只是其自然而已
I didn't mean to, okay? It just happened.
我只是想近距x看看她
Like, I-I wanted to see her up close.
所以你...  就像Bh⑹忠痈她
So you... just stalked her like a serial killer.
誊绾臀腋愿意Q之"做功n"
Josie and I prefer to call it "research."
"誊绾臀"
"Josie and I."
"Josie and I"?
怎么又砹"誊绾臀"
Wha-- how in the hell is there a Josie and I?
我也不知道
I don't know.
-我只是想知道  -想知道什么
- I just had to know. - Know what?
托比  @事ξ碚f比^特殊
Toby, one of these things is not like the other, okay?
我想知道  她是不是暮芘p肥成@拥
So I wondered, like was she fat and then she got skinny?
她是不是的人  可答案都是"不"
Was she a terrible person? But no.
她是那么美貌  出拔萃
She's actually beautiful, and she's great,
她夸我很棒
and she thinks that I'm great,
她o店里M的也很有品味
and she has amazing taste in imported goods.
摸摸@
Like, feel this.
我根本不知道@是啥|西
I don't even know what that is!
是公文包
It's a portfolio.
我很喜g
And I liked it.
那N是你喜g的型
Is that what you want?
是你喜g的  你是不是喜g身材窈窕的人
Is that what you want? Do you want a skinny person?
不是  不^我喜g和正常人在一起  P特
No, but I would like to be with a sane person, Kate.
@可不好
That is not nice.
好吧  也S我已φf好倦了
Yeah, well, maybe I'm a little tired of being nice.
有陌生人f你很棒  你就信了
Some stranger tells you that you're great and you believe her.
可是我f你很棒  你就X得我在_你
I tell you you're great and you think I'm lying.
到底槭裁
Why is that?
我不...  我不知道  我有}
I don't... I don't know. I have a problem.
我都有一堆}  P特
We all have problems, Kate.
托比  我的一生...
Toby, all of my life...
你一直很胖
You've been fat.
我知道
Yeah, I get it.
我很理解你
I empathize, clearly.
我理解你  所以逗你_心
I empathize, then I say something cute,
你高d起  然后又消沉  如此反
then you feel better, rinse and repeat.
她ξ液茉愀  P特
She was terrible to me, Kate.
誊  @身材窈窕又成功的女人
Josie, this skinny, successful woman
你真的那么崇拜她
that-that you admire so much?
她出了  她_了我
She cheated on me, she lied to me,
然后拿走了我一半的e蓄
and then she took half my life savings.
她x_我一年后
I gained 95 pounds
我w重一下L了近九十斤
in one year after she left me.
在我最低谷的r候  我跟我弟弟f
At my lowest point, I told my brother
我要自  然那不是真的
that I was committing suicide even though that wasn't true
我只是想他和我一痈械娇趾凸陋
because I wanted him to be as scared and lonely as I was.
你知道  你知道  其...
You know what? You know what? That's...
我]f  我...
That's a lie, I, uh...
我_想^自
I did consider suicide.
很多次
A lot.
那r候我以酒渤
When I would get drunk,
形斡爸
alone,
B自己都鹤约
and disgust myself.
所以  面R}的并不只有你一  P特
So, you haven't cornered the market on problems, Kate.
天啊  我在很抱歉
God, I'm really sorry.
我的啦一夜之g消云散  托比
My issues are not gonna go away overnight, Toby.
好吧
Well...
我也不
neither am I.
不^  P特...
But Jesus, Kate...
誊绾臀
Josie and I
以前相并不愉快
weren't good together.
今后也不
So we're not.
不管怎  我是要去她那里打工
It's not like I was gonna keep the job anyway.
但你知道l和l相很愉快
But you know who are good together?
R特・诙和_S{・格思里
Matt Lauer and Savannah Guthrie?
《今日秀》目的主持人搭n
我鬯z
I love them.
我希望他成槲业募胰
And I want them to be my family.
有我z
And also us.
我在一起相也特e愉快
We're pretty good together.
但我主要在fR特・诙和_S{・格思里
But mostly I was talking about Matt and Savannah.
我能留著@公文包
Can I keep the portfolio?
天啊  真要命
Oh, my God, you're killing me.
不行
No.
你就不想摸一下
Do you just want to feel it?
天啊
Oh, my God.
@是什么啊
What is that?
是小什么的
That's a baby something.
oP特留言
Leave a message for Kate.
是我
Hey, hey, it's me.
我拿下那角色了
I got the part.
算是...  很棒吧
Yay, right? I think.
能o我回  就是...
Can you call me? Uh, it's just, you know,
一般都是你告V我有多棒
you're-you're usually the one who... who tells me how great I am,
而你不在我身
and you're not here.
所以...
So...
天  苔z今晚演的白雪公主不一般啊
Man, that Tess was some Snow White tonight, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我好像冒犯到你了
I've offended you somehow.
-]有  -不  我有
- No. - No, I have.
-你X得我是在u判你  -我...
- You think I'm judging you. - I...
因槲]Y格δ闫奉^足
Because I'm in no position to judge you whatsoever.
但是你要知道
But you need to know,
如果我有Y格u判你
if I was in a position to judge you,
那也是很高的ur
you'd be getting a very high score.
那段在匹堡秃谌和上W的v
That story you told about helping to bus little black kids in Pittsburgh.
-86年  87年的事  -差不多吧
- That was '86, '87? - Thereabout.
你那r]吸毒
So you were clean then?
能正常生活
Just... functional?
你知道我@黑人小孩那r的情r
Because you know what this little black kid was doing?
-我不...  -我是孩子
- I don't... - I was a little boy,
住在e州的伯特利公@
living in Bethel Park, Pennsylvania.
那生活的大多是白人
Which is pretty much the whitest place on Earth.
我有小本本
I had this little notebook...
每次我新JR一黑人
and every time I met a new black person,
就在那小本本上擞一下
I would put a mark in this notebook.
每次遇一黑人男子  我就心想
And every time I met a black man, I wondered if, somehow,
@男人有]有可能是我父H
if that man could possibly be my father.
但我不能f
But I couldn't say that.
不能f出
You know, I couldn't say it out loud
因槲畚腋赣H
because I loved my father.
我的白人父H
My white father.
有我的白人母H
And my white mother.
我是刃大  事I有成的黑人
I'm a strong, successful, black man.
我和我妻子在育悍矫
My wife and I give a lot of thought
-真的花了很多心思  -我信
- to how we raise our girls, believe that. - Yes.
我女翰挥X得自己演白雪公主
The fact that my daughter doesn't find anything unusual
有何不妥
about her playing Snow White?
就wF了@教育理念
That's the whole idea.
Π
Right?
我并非o所不知  威廉
Look, I-I don't know everything, William.
不是
I don't.
但我ξ业母改负M意
But I wouldn't change a thing about my parents,
τ悍绞揭M意
or the way that I parent,
-我不榇说狼  -你也不
- and I will not apologize for any of it. - You shouldn't.
-因槲也挥X得抱歉  -我道歉
- Because I don't. - I should.
我JR你三星期了
Three weeks I've known you,
我]跟你f那句
and I still haven't said the words.
-你不必f什...  -Σ黄
- You don't have to say any... - I'm sorry.
我非常抱歉
I am so deeply sorry.
我做了Σ黄鹉愕氖
I did everything wrong by you.
而你每件事都做得很
And you've done everything right.
邮伦龅枚己芎  鹤
You are doing everything right, son.
那么
Well, uh...
你明早散步r  想穿什么就穿什么
Now, you wear whatever you want on your walk tomorrow.
我挺喜g@l新卡其的
Oh, I like my new flat front khakis just fine.
-f啥  -P文叔叔
- Baby say what? - Uncle Kevin!
-你好  -很好
- How are you? - Good.
-你怎么  -很好  你呢
- How you doing? - I'm good, how are you?
-你真漂亮啊  -xx
- Oh, you look beautiful. - Thank you.
H鄣  瞧  P文砹
Honey, look, it's Kevin.
-你好啊  弟弟  -你好
- What's up, bro? - Yo!
-最近好  -就那
- What's going on, man? - Oh, you know.
想念我的小粉z
Missing my fan club, of course, you know?
你不介意我鹤∫幌掳
And, uh, you don't mind if I crash for a bit, right?
-然行了  -就一段rg
- Absolutely. - For a time.
-行啊  -xx
- Yeah. - Thanks.
P文叔叔  我演了白雪公主
Uncle Kevin, I was Snow White!
-是  -你砜纯磁牡囊l
- Yeah? - You should come see the video, and
我要o史黛西・克R恩打
we have to call Stacy Klein,
她不相信你是我叔叔
who doesn't believe you're my uncle.
不是吧  搞什么啊
You're kidding me, that's ridiculous.
好  我R上就^去
All right, yeah, I'll be right there.
我跟她打招呼
We'll tell her what's up.
-她太人喜g了  -是啊
- She's cute. - Yeah, she is.
-P文  @是...  -l啊
- Uh, Kevin, this is, uh... - Yeah?
威廉  他是我...
William, he's my, uh...
@是我生父
This is my biological father.
我ふ疑父了  找到了
Whom I looked for, and I found,
就是他了
and this is him.
@事得跟我好好聊聊啊
Uh, well, that probably is gonna be a longer conversation,
但很高dJR你
but it's good to meet you.
幸
It's a pleasure to meet you.
P文叔叔  快
Uncle Kevin, come on!
-去吧  -好  我先^去了
- Uh, go. - Okay. All right, yeah, no.
-我走吧  -去吧  去吧
- Let's go. - Go, go, go, go. Yes, yes.
我家安妮呢
All right, where's my little Annie, huh?
我想念另一小粉z啊
I miss the other half of my fan club.
他是上那"奶爸"
Was that the Man-ny?
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我特e喜g那部
I love that show.
我去拿本找他名
I'm gonna go get my autograph book.
@r候f想再要一孩子是不是不合m
Hey, is now a bad time to mention having another kid?
你在看
Are you reading?
我快看完了  我看完吧  H鄣
I'm on the last page, come on, baby.
-好  -拜托了
- Yeah. - Please.
字幕M
ZiMuZu.tv
原翻g  pZ字幕
H供W 禁止用于任何商I盈利行
最新最快海外影字幕下d
登www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻g:  青椒  Tracy-旋子  小泡椒  小尼克  桑葚
翻g:  小子  冬麟  吸吸粒呀  劫Bobby
校:  不高d童鞋  t
rgS:  格瑞特  ccisoda
后期:    精校&O:  tGabriel